Regarding statutory issue.
So for ballot reconciliation there are
few things need to be performed.
First is pre PC metadata increase.
We have already made entries into job
metadata right?
If any table is having balance metrics,
there are two columns in job metadata
which are count check threshold indicator
and amount balance threshold indicator.
We have to mark them as Y if we have any
of these balance indicator.
As of now I have implemented for policy
right.
For policy I have amount columns that is
the reason why I have marked amount
balance sheet indicator as Y and we have
to make entries for all the balance
metrics into balance reconciliation
metadata table.
OK, I'll show you that, post it.
So after that,
we have to add that balance
reconciliation flow part in the IDMC
mapping.
OK.
And the third thing is we have to yeah,
Bharat.
So first thing is I'll show everything.
Yeah, I'll show everything.
I'm just informing you what are the that
we have to perform for this?
Sure.
I'll show you one by three.
Third one is we have to add 2 parameters
which are related to this balance sheet
translation into the parameter file.
OK, yeah, that's it.
These three are the things.
Let me show you 1 by 1.
So if you see the entry in job metadata,
as I have amount columns,
I mark this amount balance check
indicator as well.
OK.
If we have any count related check how we
have done for broker party address some
we'll take one dummy balance metric to
get to calculate the diction count of one
column, right.
So if we have any such kind of metrics,
we have to enable this as of as we have
only one columns,
we have enabled this in job metadata
table coming to balance reconciliation
metadata.
So this is this indicator is per that
column right In job metadata for each we
have a job level only.
Oh, OK.
So that in that while yeah,
if we give Y then in that case our ABC
framework will know OK,
Balance checks are there for this table.
We have to implement balance
reconciliation in the post.
That is it OK,
so the this these are the entries for
balance reconciliation metadata.
So this idea would be automatically
generated.
This would be just description.
Just follow this what wherever I have a
column name, right?
Just update your column name and update
the source zone and target zone
correspondingly.
If you are balancing type is amount,
keep here amount.
If it is count,
you have to keep count as our CCO is
refined to rate zone to data domain.
I kept this and then target database name,
target schema name,
target table name and target column name.
All the amount columns for which we are
performing the balance you cancellation,
source region,
source path are not related to us and we
are not choosing source query or target
query as we are using as we are
implementing source related stuff in the
stage mapping itself and target related
in the reusable balance reconciliation
itself.
That's why we don't need these two and
threshold type.
It can be either percentage or value.
But for CC work I just suggested to use
5% as the threshold value.
So I kept threshold type as percentage
and threshold value as 5.
If you have value,
keep here value and give the
corresponding value here.
And yeah,
this is just active indicator and then
ordering columns last we have job ID.
So how we have like this job ID is also
again a primary key in the documented
data tip.
I made entries to,
I made entries in the contract Excel
document where we are keeping all the ABC
metric data entries, right?
You can take reference of it.
So there I framed the query in such a way
that we can pull it using some static
values.
This job ID how we pulled for other
jobless and all OK this is this part is
done next going I'm going I'm moving to
mapping allow me to.
As we are implementing all the ABC
related in the source to stage mapping,
I have implemented the balance
reconciliation also in the same mapping.
So here this is the one.
This flow is related to balance
reconciliation.
OK,
so here whatever the records that are
intended to load into the stage table,
we are performing balance reconciliation
on the same so output group.
So if you see we are not routing issued
records or invalid records or no change
records into the target table, right.
Basically it's stated yeah, we we send.
So we would be calculating only amount
like aggregated functions.
We are applying aggregated functions only
on those records.
That is the reason why it took only those
records to this flow.
After this in the aggregated
transformation in the group by section I
use a job run ID as it is same for every
record OK.
It will take all the records basically
whatever coming from this flow.
OK.
And then in the aggregated I have
calculated all the sums.
OK first one let me show you one by one
here I have taken I saw maximum limit for
a decimal value is 28.
So here we can take 28 and out of 28
precision 6 is we are considering it for
the scale.
That means decimal values like that we we
can consider.
Otherwise 22 is also fine.
Guy 3.
Yes, I should.
Yeah,
correctly I'm taking 6 decimal points for
now.
This is fine, right?
For now.
OK.
But yeah, I already pinged in.
Maybe we can.
Yeah.
OK.
Like if you if we get any update,
we can update the precision that's it.
But the maximum limit is 28 out of 28.
Six is used for decimal points.
OK so similar.
So let me show you the expression how I
have framed these.
I'm like my intention is just to
calculate the sum of limit amount.
But there may be chances of getting null
values into these columns correct?
So in order to handle that null value if
if the if all the columns are having null
then the overall sum would be null.
In that case I just want to have a 0.
If there are few nullable values,
few non nullable values then it will take
the correct time then I I need this
otherwise if all the values are true
values then also it will consider this.
Basically my intention here is to
calculate some of the amount value and
here I'm just handling null null values
also that's it.
OK that is so here whatever the amount
columns that I have,
I created expressions for each and every
column posted in the expression
transformation using these all using all
these agreement aggregated sum values,
I have created an expression like this.
So first will be your column name and
then column aggregated value.
So if you let me show you how it looks in
balance reconciliation timetable,
it will be basically all the column
column value would be separated by column
and each column related information will
be separated by like whole in the whole
aggregate expression source aggregate
expression each column details will be
separated by pipes in the.
So this will be in this table will be in
Snowflake or it will be in our temp table,
this in Snowflake to have like as we need
to enable this full PDO,
we have this balance for now.
Here we have in in temp, we have nothing.
Yeah.
So here once we frame this aggregated
expression,
we are just populating it into the
temporary balance reconciliation table
where job ID, execution run ID,
job run ID and source the text and audit
columns.
Our intention is to have this expression
in some tables so that we can use it in
the post load.
OK.
I'm very ensured.
Hi Aishwarya, yes, this copy.
So in the mapping,
while you're adding the amount section,
right,
like for the balance reconciliation,
are you making changes to any other
components over there or only like you'll
be adding the balance reconciliation part?
Yeah.
Should we make the changes?
Yeah,
I didn't make any changes in the above in
the like for like in these two,
in these two and even in the router also
I haven't done any change.
Only thing I'm considering only the
records that are intended to load into
stage table.
I'm considering those records.
And from here only this is the this is
the only balance reconciliation part that
I have added in this mapping.
OK.
Oh, understood.
Thank you.
And here I got the aggregated text.
This is the.
So just like any other ABC temporary
table in Snowflake,
we would be also having this balance
reconciliation timetable under every
common schema under common schema of
every domain.
OK, I copied this here I'll show you.
So this is how it will give arsenal
amount zero.
I told you that it will take 6 decimal
points.
So all these values are null and only
premium amount and renewal amount is
having true values.
So that is the aggregated space holding
and for rest all it is taken as zero.
OK, OK,
this part is done in the mapping coming
to parameter file,
so in the parameter file policy.
So in the parameter file under job postal
success,
so we have job post load success under
our job level task flow rate.
So under this we have to add 2 filters
related to the balance reconciliation.
1 is target expression,
the other one is target balance Recon
filter target expression in in the sense
I'll be using this expression directly in
the seller clause.
So I'm giving all the details because
balance reconciliation is a reusable
component.
In order to make it dynamic I'm giving
the expression here because expression
changes table to table.
That is the reason why we are making this
here and here also.
Similarly how we have in the how we have
created source aggregate expressions.
We are also trying to create the same
expression even for target values.
OK,
so first will be our column value and
then sum of column value.
This is our intention, right?
And call is is to handle and values.
That's it.
Each and every column metric could be
separated by pipe single yes, Bharat.
So in the mapping, right,
we actually have a scenario like where
the column name changes in the source
mapping and target mapping.
For example it is AMT in source but in
target it will be amount no?
OK, so I got your question here.
Also you have to consider only the target
columns not the source columns.
Column name should be of target but here
only the value should be source.
It would be source because it would it is
coming from the source right.
So whatever value that is intended to be
load into the stage table that value you
have to consider to calculate the amount
sum.
But here it should be the target value
every time because we are using these
columns to compare against the balance
reconciliation metadata also.
So here we have to coming to parameter
file.
It will be both will be same right?
Both column,
I mean column see where in the balance my
reconciliation metadata parameter file
mapping everywhere whatever the hard
coded column value that we are providing,
right that that should be the same across
only here in the mapping if you have a
different name for like here in while you
are doing the sum,
whatever the column that is intended to
be loaded that you have to consider that
aggregated sum.
OK.
So here for policy in the source query
like I'm using this original limit amount
column directly map it to this original
limit column in the target transformation
in the stage transformation OK,
in the stage table.
So that is the reason why I use it this
if you give a different alias name like
org limit Lim AMD like that,
if you have given construct that you're,
you're understanding the gist why what
I'm trying to say right here,
I understand.
Yeah,
here in the in the expression where I'm
giving the value in single course right
here you have to use the corresponding
target table columns,
target table columns, correct.
So here in that parameter file also you
have to use those column names here,
here also you have to use the same
columns because in target column names
like we have, we once it is loaded, yeah,
the column name would be same, right?
So here also the same column name right
here also column name and column value
should be separated by;
: sorry: and each and every metric would
be separated by pipe symbol.
OK this is how you have to do.
Coming to the balance we can filter.
I have added this earlier for SCD type 2
mostly.
Mostly for SCD type 2.
I was under impression that SCD type 2
works like one for an update scenario.
There would be only one record coming
from the source and the same record would
be used to expire my target tables
existing record and inserting a new
record.
But whereas after connecting with
discussing with you,
I got to know that there would be two
separating column which would handle
update and insert operation separately.
So here if there are two,
in the first scenario where if we have
one,
one record coming from the source and we
are considering only one record amount,
amount value,
while we are calculating source aggregate
transformation,
we have to consider only target active
record,
only one record 1 record amount value
only.
So the the to compare the balancing
metric.
Otherwise it would be false.
Then in that case,
we have to consider only the active
records that are inserted during the load
for SCD type, normal SCD type of flow.
But here whereas coming to our Zone 2
design,
as we'll be having separate columns for
update and insert operations,
we have to as we are doing considering
the update column, update column,
update records amount value and insert
records amount value separately,
we have to consider the same thing even
in the target case.
That is the reason why I kept it as one
equal to 1.
You can also keep directly TRUG true like
that.
You can give a boolean expression OK
whatever goes.
If you are taking 1 equal to 1 keep this
otherwise this IDM will get confused
because we have equal to here right?
Otherwise you can directly give PR you
need to.
That is also working.
I tested it, it is working OK.
OK we need to keep filter as it is
already present.
Just add this as a OK, that's it.
I I guess.
Let me show you OK,
I'll show you the balance runs, runs,
test results.
Also how it looks in in parameter file.
There are other entries right?
Like below that job post.
So we have we have this already in place
for all other things.
So even though if you if you implement
balance reconciliation,
if you are not doing it,
we have all the parameters except these
two.
But if you are implementing balance
reconciliation,
these two are the extra parameters that
you have at under this particular logger
section.
OK, OK, OK,
let me show you the results in balance
reconciliation steps.
So here if you see balance reconciliation
will have all the this is the UAID column
valuation that we it is kept as null
because that's why I'm told that this
valuation date represents the date on
which valid valuation has taken place
normal for the normal notes.
She told this value sure like need need
not be populated like that.
She told that is the reason why I kept it
as null and then it will have the
aggregated.
Values of source and target and balance
flag.
If these two are exactly balanced then it
would be Y balance flag and out of
balance value is nothing but the
difference between these two.
If it is exactly 0 then balance flag
equal to 1 and threshold flag equal to 1.
If these are not balanced balance flag
equal to Y then again it will check with
the threshold value.
If it is lies with the threshold,
then our threshold value would be Y,
otherwise it would be N.
This balance in translation metric,
you don't need to do anything here.
Reusable component will take care.
Yeah, that's it.
And if you like,
will there be any test cases added to UT
for this one, we're not adding anything.
But when you run it?
No.
When you run it,
how preload components post loads
components are getting loaded right?
This will also gets loaded in the job
post load part.
OK how we have records getting loaded
into job rule error detailed and getting
updated and job rule execution log.
The records will get inserted into this
table as part of job post load.
So it would be the process happened just
like any other ABC.
It's better to have this Utah screenshot
in Utah, right,
The final one which was shown from Arora
for Utah.
In terms of Utah,
I'm saying like is it better to have a
screenshot of the final table and I mean
capturing a screenshot from final table
and add it to the Utah document is that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it is needed.
So for the first run,
we are capturing all the things right
after drawable execution log in the post
load we have,
we can add this balance reconciliation
part screenshot and the entries, entries,
entries also you can add because the
entries have happened into the table read
entries you can add.
And in the last, if everything goes good,
our final status would be completed
straight.
Oh, OK, sure.
Yeah, because that yeah,
the addition is fine.
And also entries also how we are making
entries, displaying the entries,
how they are affected or they're impacted
during the run.
We are showing everything right as part
of ABC.
Also let's have the entries also in the
UT document metadata entries are checked.
It is there for reference.
But in case if you update this for policy,
right,
you if you update UT document for policy,
you'll be able take that as a reference.
And I will also attach the similar
screenshots.
Yeah,
we have closed duty documents already,
but it's for CC 10 policy or as this ABC
one.
I mean policy as this is there,
but balance reconciliation is added as
part of backlog.
So OK,
duty is already done for all the tables.
This balance reconciliation part is added
as part of backlog.
OK,
you can just add the screenshot just
below the job rule.
Execution log.
Post load success would be there.
Just below that you're gonna add.
That's it.
OK, OK.
Just you can stop the recording.